- That is correct.
- I knew that too.
(Penny:)Good for you, sweetie.
Okay, next question.
"What is the quantum-mechanical effect
used to encode data on hard-disk drives?"
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
- Howard?
- The answer is giant magnetoresistance.
(Leslie:)- Right.
- Hey, I buzzed in.
And I answered. It's called teamwork.
(Howard:)Don't you think I should answer
engineering questions? I am an engineer.
By that logic, I should answer anthropology
questions because I'm a mammal.
(Leonard:)Just ask another one.
(Raj:)Okay.
"What artificial satellite has seen glimpses
of Einstein's predicted 'frame dragging'?"
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
(Sheldon:)And, of course, it's Gravity Probe B.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, you have to let
somebody else answer.
(Howard:)- Why?
- Because it's polite.
(Sheldon:)What do manners have to do with it?
This is war.
(Sheldon:)Were the Romans polite
when they salted Carthage...
(Sheldon:)...to make sure
nothing would ever grow again?
(Penny:)Leonard, you said
I only had to ask questions.